Countries collection, 1540-2006 (bulk 1920-1970)
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Great Britain [see England, Ireland, Scotland, Wales]
  - Mozambique, 1977, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Nepal
    - Clippings, 1959, undated (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Audiocassette: "Women in Nepal," Horizon, WFCR, 3 Apr 1981 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Netherlands
    - Biographical materials
      - General, 1898-1964 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - Aletta Jacobs, 1921-29, undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Clippings, 1920-71, undated (Box 35, Folder 5-6)
    - Documentary film (DVD) about women's health: Vrouwenhulpverlening, ontdekken en vernieuwen, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - General, 1920-62, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Publications
      - Feminine Vignettes of the Netherlands, Vol. B-15, No. 8 Apr 1962 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - Opzÿ, radikaal feministicsh maanblad, Nov 1972 (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - Women in the Netherlands: Past and Present by Dra. M.G. Schenk, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - New Guinea (Papua)
    - Clippings, 1955-61 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Publications Things to Do in Women's Clubs series, circa 1964 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - New Zealand
    - Clippings, 1914-57 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - General, 1914-67, undated (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Women's organizations
      - Catholic Women's League of New Zealand, 1964-66 (Box 35, Folder 16)
      - Girls' Life Brigade, undated (Box 35, Folder 17)
      - National Council of Women of New Zealand, 1963-69 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Nicaragua
    - Clippings, 1945-54, undated (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Publications, 1967-87 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Report: Nicaragua, Resumen del Estudio sobre la Condicion de la Mujer Trabajadora, Comision Interamericana de Mujeres, 1957 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Women's organizations, undated (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Niger: Union of Niger Women, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Nigeria [see also Cameroon (British)]
    - Biographical materials
      - General, 1958-62, undated (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Tanimowo Ogunlesi, 1961 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Clippings, 1910-70 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - General, 1960-69, undated (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Conferences and reports
      - Adult education centers in Nigeria, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Seminar on the Participation of Women in Public Life, Background Paper prepared by Mrs. T. Ayo Manuwa, 1960 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Publications
      - A Handbook for Teachers of Home Economics by R. Omosunlola Johnston, Women's Training Centre, Abeokuta, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - perspectives nigériennes, Apr 1969 (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Women's organizations
      - General, 1966 (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Enugu Business and Professional Women's Club, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - International Women's Society, undated (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - National Council of Women's Societies (Box 36, Folder 12-14)
      - Women Voluntary Organisation, Child Care Social Services, 1961-64, undated (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Norway
    - Biographical materials
      - General (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Edith Bayles, 1921-25 (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Sigrid Hellieson Lund Always Underway: The Story of a Norwegian Woman Activist, 1982 (Box 36, Folder 18-19)
    - Clippings, 1916-71, undated (Box 36, Folder 20-21)
    - Publications, 1953-60 (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
      - Women's organizations (Box 36)
    - General, 1957-61 (Box 36, Folder 24)
      - Norges Husmorforbund (Norwegian Housewives' Association), 1962-64, undated (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Nyasaland [see Malawi]
    - Pakistan [see also Oversize materials]
      - Biographical materials
        - General, 1950-65, undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
        - Jinnah, Fatime, 1964 (Box 37, Folder 2)
        - Ra'ana Liaqat Ali Khan, 1950-68, undated (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Clippings, 1947-84, undated (Box 37, Folder 4-7)
      - General, 1956-84, undated (Box 37, Folder 8-10)
      - Publications
        - General, 1976, undated (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - Pakistan Nursing and Health Review, 1963-68 (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - Women of Pakistan, 1949 (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Women's organizations
        - General, 1956-84, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - All Pakistan Women's Association
          - General (Box 37, Folder 15-17)
            - 1954-64 (Box 37, Folder 15-17)
            - 1965-66, undated (Box 38, Folder 1-2)
          - Newsletter, 1956-68, undated (Box 38, Folder 3-4)
        - Business and Professional Women's Club, 1980-84 (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - Family Planning Association of Pakistan1962-66 (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - Pakistan Girl Guides Association, 1980-84, undated (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - Pakistan Women's Institute, 1980-83, undated (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - Women's Action Forum (WAF), 1982-84, undated (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - Women's Division, Cabinet Secretariat, Government of Pakistan
          - Pamphlets, 1980-88, undated (Box 38, Folder 10)
          - "Invisible Workers: Piecework Labour Amongst Wome In Lahore" by Farida Shaheed and Khawar Mumtaz, undated (Box 38, Folder 11)
          - "Socio-Economic Characteristics of Women in Sind" by M. B. Abbasi, 1980 (Box 38, Folder 12)
          - "A Study of Female Crime in Rural and Urban Areas of Pakistan" by Pervaiz Naeem Tariq, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Panama
      - Clippings, 1951-53, undated (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Women's Organizations, 1961-62, undated (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Paraguay
      - Clippings, 1922-48, undated (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Women's Organizations, 1953, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Peru
      - Clippings, 1928-63 (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - General, 1919-53, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, 1951, 1966, undated (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - Movimiento Civico Femenino de Peru, 1965-68 (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - National Council of Women of Peru, 1959, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - Sociedad de Ayuda al Niño Enfermo (SANE), 1964-65 (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - Soroptimismo, 1964 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Philippines
      - Clippings, 1932-71 (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - General, 1931-86, undated (Box 39, Folder 13-14)
      - Publications: Leading Philippino Women Book V by Herminia M. Ancheta, 1953 (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, 1938, undated (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - Civic Assembly of Women of the Philippines (CAWP), 1956-65, undated (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - Philippine Women's Research Collective, 1985, undated (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - Philippine Women's University, 1967-69 (Box 39, Folder 19)
    - Poland
      - Biographical materials: Mary (Lane) Zaremba
        - Photographs and medal from Red Cross service with the Polish Army, 1916-19 (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - Correspondence from Starogard, Pomerania, to cousins Lewis and Isabella Leaming Forman, 1921-24 (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Clippings, 1925-71 (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - General, 1920-48, undated (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Publications
        - General, 1931, 1968 (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - Ster, organ równouprawnienia kobiet, 1911-23 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Portugal, 1971-77 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Puerto Rico [see also Oversize materials]
      - Biographical materials: Felisa Rincon de Gautier, 1951-62, undated (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Clippings, 1920-71 (Box 40, Folder 9-10)
      - General, 1952-71, undated (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Rhodesia [see also Zimbabwe] 1951-67, undated
      - Clippings, undated (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, 1967, undated (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - National Council of Women of Southern Rhodesia, 1963-64 (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - National Federation of Business and Professional Women of Rhodesia, 1951-55 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Romania
      - Clippings, 1920-69, undated (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - General, 1957, undated (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Russia [see also Union of Soviet Socialist Republics]
      - Clippings, 1978-81, undated (Box 40, Folder 18)
      - "The Fate of Women in Russia: Documents and Memoirs," collected and edited by Gennady Bordiugov: typescript in Russian sent to Gloria Steinem, 1993 (Box 40, Folder 19-22)
    - Saint Lucia, 1963 (Box 40, Folder 23)
    - El Salvador
      - Clippings, 1947-55 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - "El Savador: Resumen del studio sobre la condicion de la Mujer Trabajadora en las Republicas Americanas, 1952-53…," Comision Interamericana de Mujeres, May 1957 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - San Marino, 1955 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Saudi Arabia [see also Regions-Middle East] 1964-71
      - Clippings, 1960-75 (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Women's Organizations, 1964-65 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Scotland, 1925-30, undated (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Senegal: Report on Centre de Bopp, 1962 (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Seychelles: Background paper on Seychelles for Seminar on the Participation of Women in Public Life, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Sierra Leone
      - Clippings, 1956-58, undated (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, 1960-65 (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - YWCA, 1965 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Singapore
      - Clippings, 1961 (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, 1961, undated (Box 41, Folder 13)
        - Pan Pacific and Southeast Asia Women's Association, Singapore Bulletin, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Somalia, 1968 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - South Africa
      - Clippings, 1930-78 (Box 41, Folder 16)
      - General, 1921-80 (Box 41, Folder 17)
      - Publications
        - Women and Children Under Apartheid Newsletter African National Congress, Issue number one, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 18)
        - N. C. W. News, National Council of Women of South Africa, 1967-69 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Spain
      - Biographical materials: Gretel Amann Martinez
        - General, 2003-06, undated (Box 41, Folder 20)
        - Writings, 1981-2000, undated (Box 41, Folder 21-22)
      - Clippings, 1909-80, undated (Box 41, Folder 23)
      - Publications
        - General, 1947-52, undated (Box 41, Folder 24-25)
        - Desde la Noche y la Niebla (Mujeres en las Cárceles Franquistas) by doña Juana Jimenez, 1978 (Box 41, Folder 26)
        - Familia Española, number 32Jun 1962 (Box 41, Folder 27)
      - Women's Organizations: Sección Femenina de Falange Española Tradicionalista y de las Juntas Ofensiva Nacional Sindicalista (FET y de las JONS), 1951-63, undated (Box 42, Folder 1-3)
    - Sri Lanka 1984 [see also Ceylon] (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Sudan
      - General, 1966-71 (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Women's Organizations (Box 42)
        - Rise Up Society (in Arabic), undated (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - Sudanese Women's Union, 1960, undated (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - Women's Graduate Society (in Arabic), undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Swaziland, undated (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Sweden
      - Biographical materials
        - General, 1921-82, undated (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - Brändström, Elsa, 1920s (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - Bremer, Frederika, 1846-1955 (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - Christina, Queen of Sweden, 1863, 1937 (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - Hesselgren, Kerstin, 1922-25 (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - Key, Ellen (Box 42, Folder 15)
        - Lindstrom, Ulla, 1962 (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - Ross, Anna, 1927 (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - Saint Bridget of Sweden, 1928 (Box 42, Folder 18)
        - Wagner, Elin, 1949, undated (Box 42, Folder 19)
      - Clippings, 1970-71, undated (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Employment, 1921-71 (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - General 1923-71, undated [see also: Regions, Scandinavia] (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Publications
        - Hertha, 5, 1969 (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - Swedish Institute publications on women, 1962-68 (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - Swedish Women on the Move by Birgitta Wistrand, 1981 (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - Swedish Women-Swedish Men by Anna-Greta Leijon, undated (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, undated (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - Frederika-Bremer-Förbundet, 1928-58, undated (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - Swedish Co-operative Women's Guild, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - Swedish Housewives' Association, 1956, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - Women's Council of the Swedish Confederation of Trade Unions, 1959 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Switzerland
      - Clippings, 1920-71 (Box 43, Folder 13)
      - Publications
        - General, 1945-1960 (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - Bericht über die Verhandlungen des Schweizerischen Kogresses für die Interessen der Frau, 1897 (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - Berufsfibel für Mädchen, 1961 (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - "Bibliographie der Schweizer Frau," 1968 (Box 43, Folder 17)
      - Women's Organizations
        - Alliance de Societes Feminines Suisses, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - Société Coopérative de Cautionnement des femmes Suisses (SAFFA), 1928-56 (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - Swiss Association for Women's Suffrage, 1951, 1962 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Syria
      - Clippings, 1911-57 (Box 44, Folder 4)
      - General, 1926-58 (Box 44, Folder 5)
      - Women's Organizations, 1956, undated (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Tahiti, 1970, undated (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Tanzania
      - Clippings, 1950-70, undated (Box 44, Folder 8)
      - General, 1956-64, undated (Box 44, Folder 9)
      - Women's Organizations
        - Tanzania Women's Service League, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - Zanzibar Women's Association, 1962-63 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Tasmania, 1956 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Thailand
      - Biographical materials: Nuethip Smerasuta, 1963 (Box 44, Folder 13)
      - Clippings, 1925-77 (Box 44, Folder 14)
      - General, 1954-62, undated (Box 44, Folder 15)
      - Publications (in Thai), undated (Box 44, Folder 16)
      - Women's Organizations, 1960, undated (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Tibet, 1928, 1951 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Togo
      - Clippings, 1958-70 (Box 44, Folder 19)
      - General, undated (Box 44, Folder 20)
      - United Nations Seminar on the Status of Women in Family Law, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 21)
      - Union des Femmes du Togo, 1960-61 (Box 44, Folder 22)
    - Tonga, 1951-64 (Box 44, Folder 23)
    - Trinidad and Tobago, 1955-66, undated (Box 44, Folder 24)
    - Tripoli [see Libya] (Box 44)
    - Tunisia
      - Clippings, 1920-71 (Box 44, Folder 25)
      - General, undated (Box 44, Folder 26)
      - Publications, 1958, 1960 (Box 44, Folder 27)
      - Women's Organizations
        - General, undated (Box 44, Folder 28)
        - Union Nationale des Femmes de Tunisie, 1958-63 (Box 44, Folder 29)
    - Turkey
      - Biographical materials: Halide Edib Adivar, 1920-64 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      - Clippings, 1910-71, undated (Box 45, Folder 2-3)
      - General, 1863-1929 (Box 45, Folder 4)
      - Publications
        - General, 1927, 1969, undated (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - Les Annales de Turque, special edition "La plu méritoire des femmes turques," Mar 1935 (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - Çiftlik, Oct 1961 (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - When Latticed Windows Opened: Experiences of an American in Turkey, by Phoebe Clary as told to Marion O. Robinson, 1969 (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - Women of Turkey and their Folk-Lore by Lucy M.J. Garnett, 1890 (Box 45, Folder 9)
      - Women's organizations
        - General, 1962, undated (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - Kadin Eserleri Kütüphanesi ve Bilgi Merkezi Merkezi Vakfi (Women's Library), 2006 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Uganda
      - Clippings, 1957 (Box 45, Folder 12)
      - Conferences: One-Day Conference, Co-ordinating Committee of Women's Organisations, 24 Apr 1965 (Box 45, Folder 13)
      - General, 1960-72, undated (Box 45, Folder 14)
      - Marriage laws, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 15)
      - Women's organizations
        - Catholic Women's Clubs of Uganda, 1966 (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - Family Planning Association of Uganda, 1966, undated (Box 45, Folder 17)
        - The Mothers' Union, 1965 (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - National Committee of Catholic Women, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - Uganda Association of University Women, 1961-66 (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - Uganda Council of Women, 1958-66, undated (Box 46, Folder 4-7)
        - YWCA of Uganda, 1963-64 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Ukraine
      - Biographical materials
        - General, 1962-65 (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - Lesia Urainka, 1963-65 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - Clippings, 1912-30, undated (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - Publications, 1923, 1962-65, undated (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Union of Soviet Socialist Republics (USSR) [see also Russia]
      - Biographical materials
        - General, 1926-74, undated (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - Breshkovsky, Catherine, 1904-34, undated (Box 46, Folder 14)
        - Kollontai, Aleksandra, 1926-31, undated (Box 46, Folder 15)
        - Kovalevskaya, Sofia, undated (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - Clippings, 1924-79 (Box 46, Folder 17-20)
      - Conferences and reports: Equality of Women in the USSR International Seminar, 1957 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - General, 1891-1987, undated (Box 47, Folder 1-3)
      - Photographs: Soviet women working in fields, 1947 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Publications
        - General, 1956-87, undated (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - Soviet Women Combat Veterans of World War II [DVD], 2005 (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - Women in the Land of Socialism by Nina Popova, 1949 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Women's Organizations
        - Committee of the Soviet Women, 1964 (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - National Council of American-Soviet Friendship, 1952, undated (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - United States
      - Bibliographies, 1931-78, undated (Box 50, Folder 1-2)
      - Clippings, 1920-40, 1970-82, undated (Box 50, Folder 3-4)
      - General, 1959-77, undated (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - Great American women
        - Clippings, 1925-66 (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - "Great Women: a biographical card game," three decks: "Foremothers," "Founders & Firsts," and "Poets & Writers," 1979 (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - Hall of Fame, New York University, 1920-57 (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - Pamphlets, 1933-77, undated (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Publications
        - "The American Female," special supplement of Harper's, Oct 1962 (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - National Farm and Garden, Jul 1961 (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - Scholastic: The American High School Weekly, Woman's Number, 15 May 1937 (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - Superacion y Aporte de La Mujer Norteamericana by Anita Arroyo, Habana, Cuba, 1959 (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - USIS Feature, "U.S. Women Today," #16-17, 1967 (Box 50, Folder 14-15)
        - Women in America, and Ideals publication, 1975 (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - Women in American Life: Selected Readings edited by Ann Firor Scott, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Women's Organizations, 1941-64, undated (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Colonial women, 1924-75, undated (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Revolutionary war, 1775-1975, undated (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Civil War
        - General, 1863-1971, undated (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - An Appeal For Peace, by "Women of Maryland," 1861 (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - Ladies Army Aid Society 1861-circa 1865 (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - "Michigan Women in the Civil War," published by the Michigan Civil War Centennial Observance Commission, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - James S. Rogers: typed copies of letters, 1862-63 (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - Susie King Taylor: clipping, 1966 (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - "Rebecca Wright-Traitor or Patriot?" bu Sylvia G. Dannett, 1963 (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - My Story of the War: A Woman's Narrative of Life and Work in Union Hospitals and in the Sanitary Service of the Rebellion by Mary A. Livermore, 1888 (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - The War-Time Journal of a Georgia Girl by Eliza Frances Andrews, 1908 (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - Women of the War; Their Heroism and Self-Sacrifice by Frank Moore, 1867 (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - Women's Work in the Civil War: A Record of Heroism, Patriotism and Patience by L.P. Brockett and Mrs. Mary P. Vaughan, 1867 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Twentieth century
        - General, 1897-1953, undated (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - World War I
          - General, 1915-26, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 2)
          - "Anne Morgan: An American in France," a film by Joanne Burke about Anne Morgan and her work with the American Committee for Devastated Regions (CARD), 1996
            - Biographical materials: photocopies and typescripts (some in French), 1927-circa 1996 (Box 54, Folder 3)
            - Contact sheets and negatives of still photographs used in film (Box 54, Folder 4)
            - Final film and archival footage: VHS and BETA CAM (4 tapes) (Box 54, Folder 5-6)
        - World War II
          - General, 1942-89, undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
          - Biographical sketches of women who served in the Navy during World War II by Marion R. Bench, circa 1982 (Box 55, Folder 2)
          - Handbook for Army Wives & Mothers and all other dependents by Catherine Redmond, 1944 (Box 55, Folder 3)
          - Prisoner of the Japs by Gwen Dew, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 4)
          - Yes, Ma'am!: The Personal Papers of a WAAC Private by Elizabeth R. Pollock, 1943 (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - "What Really Happened to Rosie the Riveter?" by Sheila Tobias: typescript, undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - Vietnam War: Record of the Women's Hearing on the War in Vietnam, Christ Church Cathedral, St. Louis, Missouri, June 17, 1972 (Box 55, Folder 7-8)
        - American Revolution Bicentennial Administration, Women's Bicentennial Programs, 1974-75, undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - Regions and States
        - Appalachia, undated (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - New England
          - General, 1977, undated (Box 56, Folder 2)
          - New England Freedmen's Aid Society
            - General, 1867-68, undated (Box 56, Folder 3)
            - Education Committee, 1864-66 (Box 56, Folder 4-6)
        - South
          - General, 1977-81, undated (Box 56, Folder 7)
          - Miss Rutherford's Scrapbook: Valuable Information About the South, Vol. II, Apr 1924, Jul 1924 (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - West
          - General, 1972-78 (Box 56, Folder 9)
          - Pioneer Women: Selections From Their Journals Read by Sandy Dennis and Eileen Heckart, two audiocassettes, 1974 (Box 56, Folder 10)
          - "Three Score Years and Ten," Life-Long Memories of Fort Snelling, Minnesota and Other Parts of the West by Charlotte Ouisconsin Van Cleve, 1895 (Box 56, Folder 11)
        - Alabama, 1953-55 (Box 56, Folder 12)
        - Alaska, 1952-58 (Box 56, Folder 13)
        - Arkansas: Belle Starr: The Female Desperado, by S.W. Harman, 1954 (Box 56, Folder 14)
        - California, 1859, 1908 (Box 56, Folder 15)
        - Colorado, 1958-76, undated (Box 56, Folder 16)
        - Delaware: "Delaware's Women Today: Preliminary Report of the Governor's Commission on the Status of Women," 1964 (Box 56, Folder 17)
        - District of Columbia: Fifth Annual Report, Commission on the Status of Women, 1972 (Box 56, Folder 18)
        - Hawaii, 1865-1931 (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - Illinois, 1977-80, undated (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - Kansas, undated (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - Massachusetts
          - General, 1915-75 (Box 57, Folder 4)
          - B ehind Eternity: Holyoke Women Who Made a Difference by Marcella R. Kelly, 1973 (Box 57, Folder 5)
          - Hestia Art Collective mural, "History of women in Northampton from 1600 to 1980" 1982 (Box 57, Folder 6)
          - Letter to George Watson by Priscilla Cotton, Plymouth, 6 Nov 1845 (Box 57, Folder 7)
          - "Women of Springfield's Past," 1976, undated (Box 57, Folder 8)